similartech.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 22, 2018

### Introduction

SimilarTech Ltd. and SimilarTech Inc. (collectively " **SimilarTech** " or " **Company** " or " **we** " or " **us** " or " **our** ") is the sole owner of an analysis tool which enables its business partners or potential clients to receive insights (i.e., market research, trends, leads, etc.) to leverage and grow their businesses (" **Platform** "). SimilarTech interacts with current and prospective clients and the general public via its Website, available at: https://www.similartech.com (" **Website** ") or Service. This privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") describes our practices of processing data from visitors to the Website or from our clients and partners (" **Business Partners** ") once they register to receive our API, analytic data, insights and filtered dashboard tool (all, collectively the " **Service** "). 

For more details regarding the terms and conditions of our Services and Platform, please read our Terms of Use, available at: https://www.similartech.com/terms. Note that, this Privacy Policy is an integral part of the Terms of Use (collectively the " **Agreement** "). 

We have included below information about which data is collected, how we process and use your data, but before we would like to explain the basis on which we do so:

  1. Where you sign up for any of our services, we process your personal data in order to perform our contract with you; 
  2. If we have a legitimate interest in processing data, such as for direct marketing or online identifiers when you access our Website; or 
  3. We will also process your personal data where you have provided us with consent to do so. 

### What Type of Information We Collect

Depending on your interaction with us (meaning, if you are just browsing our Website, or if you have registered to our Services and opened an account, etc.), we may collect two types of information you, as follows: 

  * Non-Personal Data: The first type of information is non-identifiable information which may be made available or gathered through your use of the Services. To clarify, we are not aware of your identity due to such information (" **Non-Personal Information** "). The Non-Personal Information which is being collected may include your aggregated usage information and technical information transmitted or automatically collected such as (but not limited to): the time and date you access our Website, your actions within our Services (e.g., registration, pages viewed, etc.) and approximate geo-location (country level). 
  * Personal Data: The second type of information is individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes either: (i) contact information such as your name, email address, etc., which you have submitted voluntarily; or (ii) your Internet Protocol (" **IP** ") addresses (the addresses of computers on the Internet). Note that, while IP is considered personally identifiable information in many jurisdictions (such as the EEA), there are some jurisdictions in which such data is not considered as Personal Information. Therefore, we treat such information as Personal Information, in accordance with applicable laws, however we do not attempt to analyze or determine your identity based on such information or otherwise combine it with any Personal Information such as your name or email address. The IP is collected by our third party analytic partners that offer ways to opt-out, all as detailed below. 

You are not required by law to provide us with any information. You can always avoid from providing us certain Personal Information; however, you acknowledge that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Services. For example, if you are a Business Partner, we will not be able to provide you with access to the Platform if you do not provide us with the information required through the registration process. In the event we combine Personal Information with Non-Personal Information, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined. 

**_Information we collect from visitors of our Website_**

**Type of Information**

**How Do We Use It?**

In the event you contact us for support or other inquiries, either through the **online form** available on the Website, by sending us an email or by other means of communications we make available, you will be requested to provide us your name and email address. 

We will use this information solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiries and provide you with the support or information you have requested. 

In the event you have submitted a request to schedule a call, or a **request to see a demo of our Platform** , you will be requested to create an account and provide us with name, email and phone number (as applicable). 

In the event you have used the request to schedule a call feature, we will send you a welcome email in order to activate your Account. In addition, our support team will send you an email which will include further instructions regarding the Service you were interested in. We will use your phone number for the purpose of providing you the services you have requested through this feature. 

In the event you will wish to **submit a comment related to and of the posted blogs** available in the Website, you will be required to provide us your name and email address. You may also subscribe to receive follow up comments. 

We will use this information solely for the purpose of submitting your comment, for authentication purposes, or, if applicable in order to send you the follow up comments you have requested.  
Note that, we recommend you do not disclose Personal Information through the content of your comment. This comment shall be publicly posted and we cannot control any third party's use of such information. 

In the event you are interested in joining our team, and wish to submit your CV, you will be required to provide us your name, email address, and CV. 

Your provision of personal information in connection with recruiting is voluntary, and you determine the extent of information you provide us. We do not request or require sensitive personal information concerning religion, health, sexual orientation, or political affiliation in connection with recruiting. We will use the information you have provided solely to communicate with you, to manage our recruiting and hiring processes, and for compliance with corporate governance and legal and regulatory requirements. If you are hired, the information may be used in connection with employment and corporate management. 

If you voluntarily **subscribe to our newsletter** you will be asked to provide us with your email address. You can unsubscribe at any time using the unsubscribe option within the body of the newsletter or rather or by contacting customer support at [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com)

We will use your email address in order to send you information related to our Services and to keep you up to date regarding new Services, as well as provide you with tips related to sales strategy. 

**IP**

We (directly or by third part service providers as detailed below) may collect our visitors' IP. We use this for our legitimate interests of operating, providing, maintaining, protecting, managing, customizing and improving our Website and Services and the way in which we offer them; (ii) enhancing your experience with the Services; and (iii) our legitimate interests of auditing and tracking usage statistics and traffic flow. 

We also collect certain **technical Non-Personal Information** (as detailed above) which relates to your use of the Website. 

We use this technical data in order to operate and manage our Website. 

**_Information We Collect from Business Partners_**

**Type of Information**

**How Do We Use It?**

In order to use our Services (including the free trial) you will be required to register and open an account. During the registration flow you will be requested to provide us with certain information such as your email address and phone number. You may also provide us with your name, and company name. Further, during the registration process you will be required to create a password, at which time you thereby represent and warrant that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your details and password. You represent and warrant that you will not provide us with inaccurate, misleading or false information.  
You may also choose to sign in with your Google+ account. Such network account may provide us with access to certain information about you as stored therein (e.g. full name, e-mail and any other information which you made public). 

We will use this information for the purpose of performing our contract with you, provide you with the Services you have requested, and designate your account in order to display the applicable information on your account dashboard. We will use your email address and phone number in order to send you needed information related to the Services and our business engagement (e.g., send you a Welcome massage, to notify you regarding any updated to our Services, send applicable invoices, and additional occasional communications related to the Services) as well as verify your identity. 

as part of the Services (following the free trail) you will need to provide us with your **payment details**. 

We do not collect your payment details. We employ third party payment processors and thus, your payment details will be subject to such third-party payment processors privacy practices. Currently we use BlueSnap which its privacy policy is available at: <https://www.bluesnap.com/privacy-policy/>

We also collect certain **technical Non-Personal Information** (as detailed above) as a visitor to the site and as detailed above. 

See the table above. 

### _Publicly Available Information_

Our Services are provided due to a technology we have developed that analyzes millions of websites daily, and collects, gathers and analyzes information made public, this information includes mostly technical, analytic and aggregated data on market trends, online traffic, comparison between services and the technologies your competitors may be using, however, this may also include names, contacts (such as email) and titles. Even though this data was made publically available by an individual, we respect the privacy and rights of such individual and thus, this Privacy Policy governs also their rights as detailed below. 

### How We Collect Information

Depending on the nature of your interaction with the Services, we may collect information as follows: 

  1. **Automatically** \- we may use Cookies (as elaborated in the Section below) to gather some information automatically. 
  2. **Provided by you voluntarily** \- we will collect information if and when you choose to provide us with the information, such as through a registration process, newsletter registration, contact us communications, etc. all as detailed in this Privacy Policy. 

### Cookies

We may use our third-party service provider's software technologies known as " **cookies** " to collect and store information related to your interactions with the Services. A "cookie" is a small piece of information that a website assigns to your device while you are viewing a website. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various different purposes. These purposes include allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, remembering your preferences and making the interaction between you and the Services quicker and easier. We also use cookies for internal analytics purposes in order to improve our Services. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your device. Each browser is different, but generally users can remove cookies by following directions provided in the browser's "help" file. Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that, if you reject cookies or disable cookies, some features of the Website may not function properly. 

We may permit third parties to use cookies or other technology to collect information about your online and application usage activities across our Website, such as: 

  * **Google Analytics** this cookie is placed in order to track and analyze the use of our Services, for internal purposes. To learn more about how Google uses data from our use of Google Analytics Cookies, we recommend you review Google's policies located at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners>. We also encourage you to review the Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web tool available at: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 
  * **Intercom** which privacy policy can be found at: <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy>; 
  * **Hubspot** which privacy policy can be found at: <https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy>. 

### With Whom Do We Share The Information, And For What Purpose

We do not share any **Personal Information** collected from you with third parties or any of our partners except in the following events: 

  * **Third Party service providers** \- share your information with third parties that perform services on our behalf (e.g. API providers, payment process, tracking, servers, service functionality and support, marketing, etc.) these third parties may be located in different jurisdictions; 
  * **Law Requirement** \- we will share your information, solely to the extent needed to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request (i.e., to comply with courts injunction, etc.); 
  * **Policy Enforcement** \- we will share your information, solely to the extent needed to enforce our policies including investigations of potential violations thereof or to detect, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or other wrongdoing, suspected fraud or security issues; 
  * **Company's Rights** \- we will share your information, solely to the extent needed to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims; 
  * **Third Party Rights** \- we will share your information, solely to the extent needed to prevent harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users, yourself or any third party or for the purpose of collaborating with law enforcement agencies or in case we find it necessary in order to enforce intellectual property or other legal rights. 
  * **Corporate Transaction** \- We may share Personal Information, in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or asset sale). In the event of the above, our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We may store Non-Personal and Personal Information on our servers or our cloud servers, use or share Non-Personal Information in any of the above circumstances, as well as for the purpose of providing and improving our Service as detailed above. Furthermore, we reserve the right to use, disclose or transfer (for business purposes or otherwise) aggregated and processed data to third parties, including, inter alia, affiliates, for various purposes including commercial use. This information may be collected, processed and analyzed by us and transferred in a combined, collectively and aggregated manner (i.e., your information is immediately aggregated with other users) to third parties. 

### Data Retention

We retain the information we collect as long as it remains necessary for the purposes set forth above, all in accordance with applicable laws, or until an individual expresses a preference to opt-out. We may at our sole discretion, delete or amend information from our systems, without notice to you, once we deem it is no longer necessary for such purposes. 

### How Do We Safeguard And Transfer Your Information

We take great care in implementing and maintaining the security of Company's Website, Services and your information. We employ industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of our users' information and prevent unauthorized use of any such. We have implemented technical, physical and administrative security measures to protect the Personal Information, including without limitation by using industry standard encryption (SSL). In addition, we limit access to your information on our servers. The data collected by us is stored in the AWS data servers, for more information regarding the data security provided by AWS, please see: <https://aws.amazon.com/security/>. For additional information regarding our security measures please see https://www.similartech.com/security. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access or abuse Company's Services, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access. 

### Your Rights, Choices And Controls of Your Personal Information

Individuals have the right to know what information we hold about them and, in some cases, to have such information communicated to them. Individuals may also ask for our confirmation as to whether or not we process their Personal Information. Subject to the limitations in applicable law, individuals may also be entitled to obtain from us the Personal Information they have provided to us in a structured, commonly-used, and machine-readable format, and may have the right to transmit such Personal Information to another party. 

The principal rights under applicable data protection law in relation to Personal Information are as follows: 

  * the right to access any information which is provided to us; 
  * the right to rectification; 
  * the right to erasure; 
  * the right to restrict processing; 
  * the right to object to processing; 
  * the right to data portability; 
  * the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and 
  * the right to withdraw consent (to the extent applicable). 

We provide you with the ability to exercise certain choices and controls in connection with our treatment of your Personal Information, depending on your relationship with us. If you wish to exercise any or all of the above rights, please contact us by email at: [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com) or contact our Data Protection Officer at: [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com) and let us know that you wish to exercise your right of access and specify what Personal Information you would like to receive. Where we are not able to provide you with the information for which you have asked, we will endeavor to explain the reasoning for this. We reserve the right to ask for reasonable evidence to verify your identity before we provide you with any such information in accordance with applicable law. In addition, the process of locating and deleting the data may take up to one (1) month in accordance with applicable law. Data privacy and related laws in your jurisdiction may provide you with different or additional rights related to the data we collect from you, which may also apply. 

### Direct Marketing

We may send our Business Partners an email or other messages about us or our Services. We may also our updates or newsletter to individuals who have registered to these services. You can remove your Personal Information from our mailing list and stop receiving promotional communications from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com). Please note that in the event you are our Business Partner, even if you unsubscribe, we reserve the right to send you service-related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions the Services, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you terminate and delete your account. If you wish to delete your Account, please contact us at: [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com). Note that, even if we will delete your account, we will not delete certain information required under applicable law or otherwise, required for the legitimate purposes of our business. For example, we will not delete any invoices sent to you as we need it for the purpose of managing our financials. 

### Opt - Out

Website Opt-out:   
You may control how your browser responds to cookies by adjusting the privacy and security settings of your web browser. Please refer to the support page of the browser you are using. In this regard, following are some links which you may find useful: 

  * Google Chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>; 
  * Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>; 
  * Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>; 
  * Safari: <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411>; 
  * Edge: <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy>; 
  * Opera: <http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/> ; 

In the event, that you have any additional complaints about your privacy rights, please initially contact the Data Protection Officer at: [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com) and we will be happy to assist you. Note that once you opt out, part of the Services provided by us might no longer be available and some features may not work if you revoke the data transfer. Please note that you have the right at any time to contact your local data protection authority. 

### Data Transfer

We may store or process your Personal Information in the United States or in other countries. If you visit our Websites or use our Services from locations outside of the United States, please note that any information you provide to us through your use of our Websites or Service may be transferred to and processed in countries other than the country from which you accessed our Websites or Service, including the United States where our central database is operated. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area ("EEA") we will take appropriate measures to ensure that your personal data receives an adequate level of data protection upon its transfer outside of the EEA. If you are a resident of a jurisdiction where transfer of your personal data requires your consent, then your consent to this Privacy Policy includes your express consent for such transfer of your data. 

### Children's Privacy

Our Service are not direct or intended for children, as follows: (i) US residents under 13 years of age; (ii) EU residents under 16 years of age; or (iii) as children are otherwise defined under applicable law. We will not knowingly solicit, collect and store Personal Information directly from children. If you are under 18, please be sure to read the terms of this Privacy Policy with your parents or legal guardians. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a User is considered as a child under applicable law, we will take steps to immediately delete its Personal Information. We request that such individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Services. If you become aware or have any reason to believe that a child has shared any information with us, please contact us at: [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com). 

### Do Not Track Disclosure

The Service does not respond to Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track signals, please see: <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>.

### Amendments

We reserve the right to periodically amend or revise this Privacy Policy at our sole discretion; such changes will be effective immediately upon the display of the revised Privacy Policy. The last revision date will be reflected in the "Last Modified" heading. Your continued use of our Services following the amendments constitutes your acknowledgement and consent of such amendments to the Privacy Policy and your agreement to be bound by the terms of such amendments. In the event of a material change we will make best efforts to display applicable notification in our Website or if applicable, notify you via email or through your Account. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, or any concerns with respect to how your privacy any information are handled, please contact us at:  
**SimilarTech LTD**  
Nahalat Binyamin 54, Tel Aviv, Israel. ZIP 6515403.  
You can also contact us via email at: [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com)

### Data Protection Officer:

If you have any requests regarding the data collected under this Policy, including without limitation, requests to remove, delete, amend, modify or transfer the data, please contact our Data Protection Officer at: [legal@similartech.com](mailto:legal@similartech.com). Please include your name, address and email address in any correspondence so that we can respond to your inquiry or request.
